### CONTACT

Phone.: +3706-3841698

Email:mindaugas.jurgelevicius@gmail.com

Adress/Living place: Lithuania Linkedin: Mindaugas Jurgelevičius

## GOALS

- Improve everyday in professional career
- · Be part of technical projects
- · Gain Certificates related with company needs
- Learn new technologies

#### **SKILLS**

- VMware
- MS Active Directory
- Fortinet products
- Sales
- FRIG
- MSSQL
- Huawei Switch
- HTML/CSS
- Python(Django)
- Angular

# LANGUAGE

- Lithuanian native
- English B2
- Russian A1

# HOBIES

- Sport
- Travelling

# MINDAUGAS JURGELEVICIUS

#### SUMMARY

Hard-working (while studying worked two jobs to get experience) with proven technical, teamwork, and communication skills. Aiming to leverage my abilities to successfully fill the Junior backend developer with Python(Django). Frequently praised as adaptable by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **NETWORK TECHNICIAN**

UAB BALTICUM TV 2019.11 - present

- -Network device configuration, scheme forming
- Technical problem solving
- Security practice installation

#### IT ENGINEER

UAB AVEDUS 2017.04 - 2019.05

- Responsible for Network devices installation and configuration to Small/Enterprise business
- Knowledge of Fortinet products as: Firewalls, Manager, Analyzer, Switches, Access points
- Fortinet NSE4 certification gained 2017

#### **SALES REPRESENTATIVE**

UAB BALTICUM-TV 2015.01 - 2018.04

- Work with new and current clients
- Selling services over phone or in customer service office
- Devices as (setup box) fix and making everything ready for client use

# **EDUCATION**

## **VILNIAUS GEDIMINO TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY**

Bachelor's Degree

Electrical Engineering 2018

# **KLAIPEDOS AUKURO GIMNASIUM**

Middle Education

2009-2013